https://megasys.com/privacy/

ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY
By accessing or using the MegaSys.com Web site, you agree to the terms of the MegaSys Computer Technologies Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. MegaSys reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Online Privacy Policy at the time of such use.
Collection of personal information – When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for Online Support or downloading software, MegaSys may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you do elect to engage in these activities, MegaSys may ask that you provide us with personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip/postal code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
When you submit personal information to MegaSys on this site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which MegaSys Computer Technologies maintains offices, including without limitation, the United States and Canada.
How your personal information is used – MegaSys collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. The information is used to register your license and rights to online technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. The information that you provide is also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about product upgrades and other products and services of MegaSys.
When you provide MegaSys with your e-mail address (as an alternative to, or in addition to, your mailing address and phone number), MegaSys may contact you via e-mail. MegaSys never releases e-mail addresses to its representatives. MegaSys also does not offer, or allow for the selling of, any user-provided information to third parties.
Updating your personal information – You have the right to access and correct your personal information at any time. You may access and correct your personal information by writing or calling MegaSys at:
MegaSys Computer Technologies
1111 – 57 Avenue N.E.
Calgary, Alberta Canada
T2E 9B2
Customer Support: (403)295-0511 (or customer.support@megasys.com)
Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us.
Privacy related complaints – If you believe that MegaSys has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write the MegaSys Online Privacy Department at the address indicated above. Please note that MegaSys Computer Technologies is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-MegaSys web sites to which megasys.com may link.
